A Guide to the Militia Commission Papers, 1777-1858
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Militia Commissions, 1777-1858., Extent: 66.71 cu. ft. (169 boxes). (Box 3-171)
  - Subseries A. Counties, 1777-1858.
    - Hardy County, 1825. (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Hardy County, 1826. (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Hardy County, 1827. (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Hardy County, 1828. (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Hardy County, 1829. (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Hardy County, 1830. (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Hardy County, 1832. (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Hardy County, 1834. (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Hardy County, 1835. (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Hardy County, 1836. (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Hardy County, 1837. (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Hardy County, 1838. (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Hardy County, 1839. (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Hardy County, 1840. (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Hardy County, 1841. (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Hardy County, 1842. (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Hardy County, 1843. (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - Hardy County, 1844. (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - Hardy County, 1845. (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - Hardy County, 1846. (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - Hardy County, 1847. (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - Hardy County, 1848. (Box 67, Folder 49)
    - Hardy County, 1849. (Box 67, Folder 50)
    - Hardy County, 1850. (Box 67, Folder 51)
    - Hardy County, 1851. (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - Hardy County, 1852. (Box 67, Folder 53)
    - Hardy County, 1853. (Box 67, Folder 54)
    - Hardy County, 1854. (Box 67, Folder 55)
    - Hardy County, 1856. (Box 67, Folder 56)
    - Harrison County, 1784. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Harrison County, 1785. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Harrison County, 1787. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Harrison County, 1788. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Harrison County, 1789. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Harrison County, 1791. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Harrison County, 1792. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Harrison County, 1793. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Harrison County, 1794. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Harrison County, 1795. (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Harrison County, 1796. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Harrison County, 1797. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Harrison County, 1798. (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Harrison County, 1799. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Harrison County, 1800. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Harrison County, 1801. (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Harrison County, 1802. (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Harrison County, 1803. (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Harrison County, 1804. (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Harrison County, 1806. (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Harrison County, 1807. (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Harrison County, 1808. (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Harrison County, 1809. (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Harrison County, 1810. (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Harrison County, 1811. (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Harrison County, 1812. (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Harrison County, 1813. (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Harrison County, 1814. (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Harrison County, 1815. (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Harrison County, 1816. (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Harrison County, 1817. (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Harrison County, 1818. (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Harrison County, 1819. (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Harrison County, 1820. (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Harrison County, 1821. (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Harrison County, 1822. (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Harrison County, 1823. (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Harrison County, 1824. (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Harrison County, 1825. (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - Harrison County, 1826. (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - Harrison County, 1827. (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - Harrison County, 1828. (Box 68, Folder 42)
    - Harrison County, 1829. (Box 68, Folder 43)
    - Harrison County, 1830. (Box 68, Folder 44)
    - Harrison County, 1831. (Box 68, Folder 45)
    - Harrison County, 1832. (Box 68, Folder 46)
    - Harrison County, 1833. (Box 68, Folder 47)
    - Harrison County, 1834. (Box 68, Folder 48)
    - Harrison County, 1835. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Harrison County, 1836. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Harrison County, 1837. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Harrison County, 1838. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Harrison County, 1839. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Harrison County, 1840. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Harrison County, 1841. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Harrison County, 1842. (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Harrison County, 1843. (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Harrison County, 1844. (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Harrison County, 1845. (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Harrison County, 1846. (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Harrison County, 1847. (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Harrison County, 1848. (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Harrison County, 1849. (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Harrison County, 1850. (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Harrison County, 1851. (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Harrison County, 1852. (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Harrison County, 1853. (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Harrison County, 1854. (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Harrison County, 1856. (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Harrison County, undated. (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Henrico County, 1784. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Henrico County, 1785. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Henrico County, 1786. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Henrico County, 1787. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Henrico County, 1788. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Henrico County, 1789. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Henrico County, 1790. (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Henrico County, 1791. (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Henrico County, 1792. (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Henrico County, 1793. (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Henrico County, 1794. (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Henrico County, 1795. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Henrico County, 1796. (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Henrico County, 1797. (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Henrico County, 1798. (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Henrico County, 1799. (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Henrico County, 1800. (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Henrico County, 1801. (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Henrico County, 1802. (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Henrico County, 1803. (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Henrico County, 1804. (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Henrico County, 1805. (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Henrico County, 1806. (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Henrico County, 1807. (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Henrico County, 1808. (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Henrico County, 1809. (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Henrico County, 1810. (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Henrico County, 1812. (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Henrico County, 1813. (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Henrico County, 1814. (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Henrico County, 1816. (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Henrico County, 1817. (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Henrico County, 1818. (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Henrico County, 1819. (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - Henrico County, 1820. (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Henrico County, 1821. (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Henrico County, 1822. (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Henrico County, 1823. (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Henrico County, 1824. (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Henrico County, 1825. (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Henrico County, 1826. (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Henrico County, 1827. (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Henrico County, 1828. (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - Henrico County, 1829. (Box 70, Folder 44)
    - Henrico County, 1830. (Box 70, Folder 45)
    - Henrico County, 1831. (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Henrico County, 1832. (Box 70, Folder 47)
    - Henrico County, 1833. (Box 70, Folder 48)
    - Henrico County, 1834. (Box 70, Folder 49)
    - Henrico County, 1835. (Box 70, Folder 50)
    - Henrico County, 1836. (Box 70, Folder 51)
    - Henrico County, 1837. (Box 70, Folder 52)
    - Henrico County, 1838. (Box 70, Folder 53)
    - Henrico County, 1839. (Box 70, Folder 54)
    - Henrico County, 1840. (Box 70, Folder 55)
    - Henrico County, 1841. (Box 70, Folder 56)
    - Henrico County, 1842. (Box 70, Folder 57)
    - Henrico County, 1843. (Box 70, Folder 58)
    - Henrico County, 1844. (Box 70, Folder 59)
    - Henrico County, 1845. (Box 70, Folder 60)
    - Henrico County, 1846. (Box 70, Folder 61)
    - Henrico County, 1847. (Box 70, Folder 62)
    - Henrico County, 1848. (Box 70, Folder 63)
    - Henrico County, 1849. (Box 70, Folder 64)
    - Henrico County, 1850. (Box 70, Folder 65)
    - Henrico County, 1851. (Box 70, Folder 66)
    - Henrico County, 1852. (Box 70, Folder 67)
    - Henrico County, 1854. (Box 70, Folder 68)
    - Henrico County, 1855. (Box 70, Folder 69)
    - Henrico County, 1856. (Box 70, Folder 70)
    - Henrico County, undated. (Box 70, Folder 71)
    - Henry County, 1785. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Henry County, 1788. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Henry County, 1789. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Henry County, 1790. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Henry County, 1791. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Henry County, 1792. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Henry County, 1793. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Henry County, 1794. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Henry County, 1795. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Henry County, 1796. (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Henry County, 1798. (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Henry County, 1799. (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Henry County, 1800. (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Henry County, 1801. (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Henry County, 1802. (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Henry County, 1803. (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Henry County, 1805. (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Henry County, 1806. (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Henry County, 1807. (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Henry County, 1808. (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Henry County, 1809. (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Henry County, 1810. (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Henry County, 1811. (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Henry County, 1812. (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Henry County, 1813. (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Henry County, 1814. (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Henry County, 1815. (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Henry County, 1816. (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Henry County, 1817. (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Henry County, 1818. (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Henry County, 1819. (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Henry County, 1820. (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Henry County, 1821. (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Henry County, 1822. (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - Henry County, 1823. (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - Henry County, 1824. (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Henry County, 1825. (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Henry County, 1826. (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - Henry County, 1827. (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - Henry County, 1828. (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - Henry County, 1829. (Box 71, Folder 41)
    - Henry County, 1830. (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - Henry County, 1831. (Box 71, Folder 43)
    - Henry County, 1832. (Box 71, Folder 44)
    - Henry County, 1833. (Box 71, Folder 45)
    - Henry County, 1834. (Box 71, Folder 46)
    - Henry County, 1835. (Box 71, Folder 47)
    - Henry County, 1836. (Box 71, Folder 48)
    - Henry County, 1837. (Box 71, Folder 49)
    - Henry County, 1838. (Box 71, Folder 50)
    - Henry County, 1839. (Box 71, Folder 51)
    - Henry County, 1840. (Box 71, Folder 52)
    - Henry County, 1841. (Box 71, Folder 53)
    - Henry County, 1842. (Box 71, Folder 54)
    - Henry County, 1843. (Box 71, Folder 55)
    - Henry County, 1844. (Box 71, Folder 56)
    - Henry County, 1845. (Box 71, Folder 57)
    - Henry County, 1846. (Box 71, Folder 58)
    - Henry County, 1847. (Box 71, Folder 59)
    - Henry County, 1848. (Box 71, Folder 60)
    - Henry County, 1849. (Box 71, Folder 61)
    - Henry County, 1850. (Box 71, Folder 62)
    - Henry County, 1851. (Box 71, Folder 63)
    - Henry County, 1852. (Box 71, Folder 64)
    - Henry County, 1853. (Box 71, Folder 65)
    - Henry County, undated. (Box 71, Folder 66)
    - Highland County, 1848. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Highland County, 1849. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Highland County, 1850. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Highland County, 1851. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Highland County, 1852. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Highland County, 1853. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Highland County, 1856. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Isle of Wight, 1785. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Isle of Wight, 1786. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Isle of Wight, 1787. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Isle of Wight, 1788. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Isle of Wight, 1789. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Isle of Wight, 1791. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Isle of Wight, 1792. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Isle of Wight, 1793. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Isle of Wight, 1794. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Isle of Wight, 1795. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Isle of Wight, 1796. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Isle of Wight, 1797. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Isle of Wight, 1798. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Isle of Wight, 1799. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Isle of Wight, 1800. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Isle of Wight, 1801. (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Isle of Wight, 1803. (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Isle of Wight, 1805. (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Isle of Wight, 1806. (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Isle of Wight, 1807. (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Isle of Wight, 1808. (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Isle of Wight, 1809. (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Isle of Wight, 1810. (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Isle of Wight, 1811. (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Isle of Wight, 1812. (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Isle of Wight, 1813. (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Isle of Wight, 1814. (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Isle of Wight, 1815. (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Isle of Wight, 1816. (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Isle of Wight, 1817. (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Isle of Wight, 1818. (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Isle of Wight, 1819. (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Isle of Wight, 1820. (Box 73, Folder 33)
    - Isle of Wight, 1821. (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - Isle of Wight, 1822. (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - Isle of Wight, 1823. (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - Isle of Wight, 1824. (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - Isle of Wight, 1825. (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - Isle of Wight, 1826. (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - Isle of Wight, 1827. (Box 73, Folder 40)
    - Isle of Wight, 1828. (Box 73, Folder 41)
    - Isle of Wight, 1830. (Box 73, Folder 42)
    - Isle of Wight, 1831. (Box 73, Folder 43)
    - Isle of Wight, 1832. (Box 73, Folder 44)
    - Isle of Wight, 1833. (Box 73, Folder 45)
    - Isle of Wight, 1834. (Box 73, Folder 46)
    - Isle of Wight, 1835. (Box 73, Folder 47)
    - Isle of Wight, 1836. (Box 73, Folder 48)
    - Isle of Wight, 1837. (Box 73, Folder 49)
    - Isle of Wight, 1838. (Box 73, Folder 50)
    - Isle of Wight, 1839. (Box 73, Folder 51)
    - Isle of Wight, 1840. (Box 73, Folder 52)
    - Isle of Wight, 1842. (Box 73, Folder 53)
    - Isle of Wight, 1843. (Box 73, Folder 54)
    - Isle of Wight, 1844. (Box 73, Folder 55)
    - Isle of Wight, 1845. (Box 73, Folder 56)
    - Isle of Wight, 1846. (Box 73, Folder 57)
    - Isle of Wight, 1847. (Box 73, Folder 58)
    - Isle of Wight, 1848. (Box 73, Folder 59)
    - Isle of Wight, 1849. (Box 73, Folder 60)
    - Isle of Wight, 1850. (Box 73, Folder 61)
    - Isle of Wight, 1851. (Box 73, Folder 62)
    - Isle of Wight, 1852. (Box 73, Folder 63)
    - Isle of Wight, 1853. (Box 73, Folder 64)
    - Isle of Wight, 1855. (Box 73, Folder 65)
    - Isle of Wight, 1856. (Box 73, Folder 66)
    - Isle of Wight, undated. (Box 73, Folder 67)
    - Jackson County, 1832. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Jackson County, 1833. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Jackson County, 1834. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Jackson County, 1835. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Jackson County, 1836. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Jackson County, 1837. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Jackson County, 1838. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Jackson County, 1839. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Jackson County, 1840. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Jackson County, 1841. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Jackson County, 1842. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Jackson County, 1843. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Jackson County, 1844. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Jackson County, 1845. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Jackson County, 1846. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Jackson County, 1847. (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Jackson County, 1848. (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Jackson County, 1849. (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Jackson County, 1850. (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Jackson County, 1851. (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Jackson County, 1852. (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Jackson County, 1853. (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - James City County, 1784. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - James City County, 1785. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - James City County, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - James City County, 1788. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - James City County, 1789. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - James City County, 1793. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - James City County, 1794. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - James City County, 1797. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - James City County, 1798. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - James City County, 1800. (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - James City County, 1801. (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - James City County, 1803. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - James City County, 1804. (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - James City County, 1805. (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - James City County, 1806. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - James City County, 1807. (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - James City County, 1808. (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - James City County, 1809. (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - James City County, 1810. (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - James City County, 1811. (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - James City County, 1812. (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - James City County, 1813. (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - James City County, 1814. (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - James City County, 1815. (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - James City County, 1816. (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - James City County, 1817. (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - James City County, 1818. (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - James City County, 1819. (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - James City County, 1820. (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - James City County, 1821. (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - James City County, 1822. (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - James City County, 1823. (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - James City County, 1824. (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - James City County, 1825. (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - James City County, 1826. (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - James City County, 1827. (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - James City County, 1828. (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - James City County, 1829. (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - James City County, 1831. (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - James City County, 1832. (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - James City County, 1833. (Box 75, Folder 41)
    - James City County, 1834. (Box 75, Folder 42)
    - James City County, 1835. (Box 75, Folder 43)
    - James City County, 1836. (Box 75, Folder 44)
    - James City County, 1837. (Box 75, Folder 45)
    - James City County, 1838. (Box 75, Folder 46)
    - James City County, 1839. (Box 75, Folder 47)
    - James City County, 1840. (Box 75, Folder 48)
    - James City County, 1841. (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - James City County, 1842. (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - James City County, 1843. (Box 75, Folder 51)
    - James City County, 1844. (Box 75, Folder 52)
    - James City County, 1845. (Box 75, Folder 53)
    - James City County, 1846. (Box 75, Folder 54)
    - James City County, 1847. (Box 75, Folder 55)
    - James City County, 1848. (Box 75, Folder 56)
    - James City County, 1849. (Box 75, Folder 57)
    - James City County, 1850. (Box 75, Folder 58)
    - James City County, 1851. (Box 75, Folder 59)
    - James City County, 1852. (Box 75, Folder 60)
    - James City County, 1853. (Box 75, Folder 61)
    - James City County, undated. (Box 75, Folder 62)
    - Jefferson County (Kentucky), 1784. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Jefferson County (Kentucky), 1785. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Jefferson County (Kentucky), 1786. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Jefferson County, 1802. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Jefferson County, 1803. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Jefferson County, 1804. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Jefferson County, 1805. (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Jefferson County, 1806. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Jefferson County, 1807. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Jefferson County, 1808. (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Jefferson County, 1809. (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Jefferson County, 1810. (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Jefferson County, 1811. (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Jefferson County, 1812. (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Jefferson County, 1813. (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Jefferson County, 1814. (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Jefferson County, 1815. (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Jefferson County, 1816. (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Jefferson County, 1817. (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Jefferson County, 1818. (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Jefferson County, 1819. (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Jefferson County, 1820. (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Jefferson County, 1821. (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Jefferson County, 1822. (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Jefferson County, 1823. (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Jefferson County, 1824. (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Jefferson County, 1825. (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Jefferson County, 1826. (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Jefferson County, 1827. (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Jefferson County, 1828. (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Jefferson County, 1829. (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - Jefferson County, 1830. (Box 76, Folder 32)
    - Jefferson County, 1831. (Box 76, Folder 33)
    - Jefferson County, 1832. (Box 76, Folder 34)
    - Jefferson County, 1833. (Box 76, Folder 35)
    - Jefferson County, 1834. (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Jefferson County, 1835. (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Jefferson County, 1836. (Box 76, Folder 38)
    - Jefferson County, 1837. (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Jefferson County, 1838. (Box 76, Folder 40)
    - Jefferson County, 1839. (Box 76, Folder 41)
    - Jefferson County, 1840. (Box 76, Folder 42)
    - Jefferson County, 1841. (Box 76, Folder 43)
    - Jefferson County, 1842. (Box 76, Folder 44)
    - Jefferson County, 1843. (Box 76, Folder 45)
    - Jefferson County, 1844. (Box 76, Folder 46)
    - Jefferson County, 1845. (Box 76, Folder 47)
    - Jefferson County, 1847. (Box 76, Folder 48)
    - Jefferson County, 1848. (Box 76, Folder 49)
    - Jefferson County, 1849. (Box 76, Folder 50)
    - Jefferson County, 1852. (Box 76, Folder 51)
    - Jefferson County, 1856. (Box 76, Folder 52)
    - Jefferson County, undated. (Box 76, Folder 53)
    - Kanawha County, 1789. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Kanawha County, 1791. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Kanawha County, 1796. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Kanawha County, 1797. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Kanawha County, 1798. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Kanawha County, 1801. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Kanawha County, 1804. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Kanawha County, 1805. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Kanawha County, 1806. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Kanawha County, 1808. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Kanawha County, 1809. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Kanawha County, 1810. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Kanawha County, 1811. (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Kanawha County, 1812. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Kanawha County, 1813. (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Kanawha County, 1814. (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Kanawha County, 1815. (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Kanawha County, 1816. (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Kanawha County, 1817. (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Kanawha County, 1818. (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Kanawha County, 1822. (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Kanawha County, 1823. (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Kanawha County, 1824. (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Kanawha County, 1825. (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Kanawha County, 1826. (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Kanawha County, 1827. (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Kanawha County, 1828. (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Kanawha County, 1829. (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Kanawha County, 1830. (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Kanawha County, 1832. (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Kanawha County, 1834. (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Kanawha County, 1835. (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Kanawha County, 1836. (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Kanawha County, 1837. (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Kanawha County, 1838. (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Kanawha County, 1839. (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Kanawha County, 1840. (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Kanawha County, 1841. (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Kanawha County, 1842. (Box 77, Folder 39)
    - Kanawha County, 1843. (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Kanawha County, 1844. (Box 77, Folder 41)
    - Kanawha County, 1845. (Box 77, Folder 42)
    - Kanawha County, 1846. (Box 77, Folder 43)
    - Kanawha County, 1847. (Box 77, Folder 44)
    - Kanawha County, 1848. (Box 77, Folder 45)
    - Kanawha County, 1849. (Box 77, Folder 46)
    - Kanawha County, 1850. (Box 77, Folder 47)